1. What are the main functional differences between a while and a for?
	- for has defined number of rep
	- while can run infinitely



2. What’s the difference between break and continue?
	- break breaks the loop
	- continue skips that particular iteration & begins the next iteration


3. When is a loop’s else clause executed?
	- when it exits successfully


4. How can you code a counter-based loop in Python?
	- use a counter var


5. What can a range be used for in a for loop?

	- a number, a set, or a function
